<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ADX Portals on Rambling Reece</title>
    <link>https://ramblingreece.co.uk/tags/adx-portals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ADX Portals on Rambling Reece</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2019 Reece Campbell</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 18:46:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ramblingreece.co.uk/tags/adx-portals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamics 365 Portals - Useful Resources</title>
      <link>https://ramblingreece.co.uk/2017/02/18/dynamics-365-portals-useful-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 18:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramblingreece.co.uk/2017/02/18/dynamics-365-portals-useful-resources/</guid>
      <description>Now that every Dynamics CRM Enterprise license comes with a CRM Portal as standard it is a good thing to get to know, not to mention it is an incredibly powerful and useful addition to an already great platform.
This post attempts to capture all of the useful references I have found to date for learning how to implement portals.The references included in this post relate to the latest version of CRM Portals which is provided with Dynamics 365 and therefore is not available to on-premise versions and does not include the ability to develop new web pages in .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish changes to CRM Portals</title>
      <link>https://ramblingreece.co.uk/2017/01/10/publish-changes-to-crm-portals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 17:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramblingreece.co.uk/2017/01/10/publish-changes-to-crm-portals/</guid>
      <description>A new feature of Dynamics 365 is the ability to add a Web Portal for access to the CRM by way of a web front end. This is a modified form of the ADX Studio Portals project bought by Microsoft previously and can be enabled directly in the Office 365 admin portal and configured via the CRM and website (with the correct user role assigned).It is a great new addition and has huge potential as a useful addition to most CRM implementations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>